vodafone.co.ug 2019-05-20

# Privacy Statement

In this privacy policy:

  * “we/us” means Vodafone Group plc;
  * “third party” means someone who is not you or us; and
  * “Vodafone Group” means Vodafone Group Plc and any company or other organisation in which Vodafone Group Plc owns more than 15% of the share capital.

Our registered office is Vodafone House, The Connection Newbury, Berkshire RG14 2FN. We are registered in England under company number 1833679. Vodafone Group PLC is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), registration number Z8088474.

### How to contact us

Your opinion matters to us – if you have any questions about our privacy statement, you can email us at: Ask.GroupPrivacy@vodafone.com or you can write to our privacy team at:

Global Privacy Team – Group Legal

Vodafone Group Services Limited

Vodafone House

The Connection

Newbury

RG14 2FN

England

### Personal information we collect about you

#### Information we collect about you

The types of information we collect about you when you visit and interact with this site are:

  * Your contact details such as name and email address where you have contacted us through this site; or
  * If you have agreed to cookies, data such as your site preferences or language settings. We can also use this information in an aggregate manner to understand how our visitors navigate this site so we can make it better.

#### When we collect your personal information

We collect your personal information when you:

  * Browse and interact with the vodafone.com website; or
  * Use our contact forms to get in touch or register your interest.

#### Vodafone will process your personal data based on:

1. **Our legitimate business interests** , for example, direct marketing and improvement of our services. Whenever we rely on this lawful basis to process your data, we assess our business interests to make sure they do not override your rights. Additionally, in some cases you have the right to object to this processing. For more information, visit the Your Rights section of this policy.

2\. **Consent you provide** where Vodafone does not rely on another legal basis. Consent will always be presented separately to you, can be withdrawn at any time and you will be given details on how to change your mind.

### How we use your personal information

#### Maintaining this website and providing you with any services requested through it

For example, when you contact us through this site, we’ll use your information to ensure you get the right information and response.

#### To personalise this website and track its performance

Because of the way this website operates, we may also use information from your browser or browsing activities to personalize the site or route you to relevant information. For example, we may use web-log information, cookies or web beacons in ways that help us maintain some of your site preferences, send you to the right country-specific information or understand how our visitors navigate the site so we can make it better.

You can choose whether or not to allow cookies or web beacons using your browser preferences. To find out more about cookies and your choices, visit the Cookies section of this statement.

### How we share your personal information

Some of the services or information you can request on this site may come from other members of our corporate family. Therefore, we may share your information with other companies within Vodafone Group (for example, your local carrier). The laws of the countries where these companies are based may not be the same as those in the EU, but your information will be treated with the same high standard of care wherever it’s processed within the corporate family.

### International data transfers

We may need to transfer your information to other Vodafone Group companies (for example, if the information you request is delivered by them) or service providers in countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA). The EEA consists of countries in the European Union, Switzerland, Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway: they are considered to have equivalent laws when it comes to data protection and privacy.  This kind of data transfer may happen if our servers (i.e. where we store data) or our suppliers and service providers are based outside the EEA, or if you use our services and products while visiting countries outside this area.

If Vodafone sends your information to a country that is not in the EEA, we will make sure that your information is properly protected. We will always ensure that there is a proper legal agreement that covers the data transfer. In addition, if the country is not considered to have laws that are equivalent to EU data protection standards then we will ask the third party to enter into a legal agreement that reflects those standards.

### How long we keep your personal information for

We’ll store your information for as long as we have to by law. If there’s no legal requirement for us to retain the data, we’ll only store it for as long as we need to.

### Keeping your personal information secure

We have specialised security teams who constantly review and improve our measures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, accidental loss, disclosure or destruction.

Communications over the internet (such as emails) aren’t secure unless they’ve been encrypted. Your communications may go through a number of countries before being delivered, as this is the nature of the internet.

We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.

We’ll never ask for your secure personal or account information by an unsolicited means of communication. You’re responsible for keeping your personal and account information secure and not sharing it with others.

Our website may provide links to third-party websites. We cannot be responsible for the security and content of such third-party websites. So make sure you read that company’s privacy and cookies policies before using or putting your personal information on their site.

The same applies to any third-party websites or content you connect to using our products and services.

You may choose to disclose your information in certain ways such as social plug-ins (including those offered by Google, Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest) or using third-party services that allow you to post reviews or other information publicly, and a third party could use that information.

Social plug-ins and social applications are operated by the social network themselves and are subject to their own terms of use and privacy and cookies policies. You should make sure you’re familiar with these.

### Your rights

Under the law, you have a number of rights that you can exercise free of charge. We have included a summary of these below; if you would like to discuss or exercise any of these, please contact us through the details provided.

#### Right to correct personal data

If you believe any of the personal data we hold about you is incorrect, you can request we update it.

#### Right to access personal data

You have a right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you, and how it has been processed.

#### Right to data portability

In some circumstances, you have the right to receive the personal information about you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party.

#### Right to object to use of personal data

Where we are processing your data for the purposes of direct marketing, or any legitimate interests that Vodafone is reliant upon, you can object at any time to this processing.

#### Right to restrict use of your data

In some circumstances, you can request that we temporarily suspend the processing of your data.

#### Right to erasure

In some circumstances, such as where we no longer have a justifiable reason to continue to process your data, you can request we delete it.

#### How to lodge a complaint

If you have a complaint, you can contact us on the details provided. We’ll do our best to help but if you’re still unhappy, you can contact the ICO, which is the UK data protection regulator – their details are at [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/).

### Our cookie policy

Cookies are tiny text files that are stored on your computer, tablet or mobile phone when you visit a website. The cookies mean that the website will remember you and how you've used the site every time you come back.

Cookies themselves don't hold personal information such as your name or bank details. And in many cases, we won’t be able to link the information we collect by using a cookie back to you.  They can, however, help us to find information once you're logged in or help us link your browsing information to you and your personal information, for example, when you choose to register for a service, white paper or newsletter.

#### Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms.

You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

  * OptanonConsent
  * OptanonAlertBoxClosed

#### Performance Cookies

These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.

All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.

  * utag_main
  * __utmz
  * __utmv
  * __utmb
  * __utma
  * __utmc
  * __utmt
  * Mbox
  * s_cc

#### Targeting Cookies

These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites.

They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

  * AMCV_B575FA8056E976CC7F000101%40AdobeOrg
  * AMCVS_xxxxxAdobeOrg
  * youtube.com

            o    SID

            o    HSID

            o    demographics

            o    VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE

            o    PREF

            o    APISID

            o    SSID

            o    LOGIN_INFO

            o    YSC  
            o    SAPISID

  * Google.com

            o    APISID

            o    SSID

            o    NID

            o    PREF

            o    SID

            o    SAPISID

            o    HSID

  * doubleclick.net

            o    id

#### First party and third party cookies

First party cookies originate from the same domain as the website you’re currently visiting, whether as third party cookies originate from a different domain.

#### Controlling your cookies

You can control how you use cookies in your browser.  If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by any website - including a Vodafone website, you should do this through the web browser settings for each web browser you use, on each device you use to access the internet.

Information on controlling and deleting cookies, including on a wide variety of browsers, is also available at allaboutcookies.org
